powersoft-audio.com 2011-12-01

# Privacy | terms-of-use-a-privacy | about

Powersoft (the "Company") is committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to www.powersoft-audio.com and as part of our commitment to privacy, we make this privacy statement. In general, you, as our customer, can visit Powersoft on the World Wide Web without having to reveal any personal information. The extent of the information that we collect depends on the information that you provide us. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us.

By registering and/or requesting information on this site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.

#### INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU

When you visit www.powersoft-audio.com you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name and contact details. We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from e-mails and/or letters you send to us. Powersoft may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes although you are under no obligation to respond.

#### USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We will use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business. In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our products, services and for marketing purposes. Furthermore, where you have consented, we might also use your information to: (i) let you know about Powersoft products and services that we offer which may be of interest to you; (ii) notify you about changes to our products and services; (iii)allow you participate in the interactive features of our website, when you choose to do so. We may contact you by post, telephone, fax as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know.

#### DISCLOSURE/ STORAGE OF YOUR INFORMATION

The information you provide to us will be held on our secure servers within the European Economic Area and may be accessed by or given to our staff working outside Italy, our parent company, subsidiaries and affiliates some of whom are located outside the European Economic Area. We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our website to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share the password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

Where you have consented when providing us with your details, we may also allow carefully selected third parties, including other companies in our group, to contact you occasionally about products and services which may be of interest to you. They may contact you by post, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted by these companies in the future, please let us know.

Countries outside the European Economic Area do not always have strong data protection laws. However, we will always take steps to ensure that your information is used by all third parties in accordance with this policy. Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

Finally, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.

#### IP ADDRESS AND COOKIES

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating systems and browser type, for administration and to report aggregate information for marketing purposes. This is statistical data about your browsing actions and patterns and it does not identify you.

Cookies are small amounts of information which we store on your computer. Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies by activating the settings on your browser although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site.

#### SECURITY AND DATA RETENTION

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

Occasionally, our website may contain electronic links to other sites. In case you choose to visit these sites, their own privacy policy and privacy preferences will apply.

#### ACCESSING AND UPDATING

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of €10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

#### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.

#### CONTACT

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to the Webmaster, [__](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'mailto:';%20var%20suffix%20=%20'';%20var%20attribs%20=%20'';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy50939%20=%20'webmaster'%20+%20'@';%20addy50939%20=%20addy50939%20+%20'powersoft-audio'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\(%20'%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20addy50939%20+%20suffix%20+%20'\\''%20+%20attribs%20+%20'%3E'%20\);%20document.write\(%20addy50939%20\);%20document.write\(%20'%3C\\/a%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20e-mail%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it%20%3Cscript%20language='JavaScript'%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\(%20'%3C/'%20\);%20document.write\(%20'span%3E'%20\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)_[webmaster@powersoft-audio.com](mailto:webmaster@powersoft-audio.com)_
